ROOPAL JAIN GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Personal Information

- 1220, Saraswati Kuni, Ardee City, Gate No.2, Gurugram
- +91-7300048248
- 🛞 roopaljain.824@gmail.com

Technical Skills

COREL ILLUSTRATOR PHOTOSHOP

Area of Interest

PRINT DESIGN
PHOTOGRAPHY
LAYOUT
ILLUSTRATION (MANUAL)
SCULPTURE

Language

ENGLISH HINDI

About

Dynamic, creative and competitive Graphical Designer with more than 3 Years experience, seeking a position in an organization with taxing and diverse working environment wherein I can learn about new prospects and industry advancements to expose and implement my knowledge.

Experience

Sr. Graphic Designer & Sr. Visuailzer

Ekaaksh Innovation Pvt Ltd | July 2017- October 2018

- Successfully manage and coordinate graphic design projects from concept and incubation through completion.
- Conceptualized and Developed Logos, Collateral's Design , Catalogues, Brochure, Canopy etc.
- Designed packaging for new and existing products and created mockup to be shared with clients.
- Designed Creatives for Web and Social Media.
- Designed Advertisement for Newspaper.

Jr. Graphic Designer

Line n Curves | August 2015 - May 2017

- Developed logos, business card, flyers, for the clients.
- Create, plan, prepare, design and generate a wide variety of visual material.
- Design layout for wedding cards and packaging.
- Assisted in creating the overall look of marketing campaigns.

Freelancer Designer

- Make Layout and Designed Logo's, business card, promotional tools, brochure, catalogs, Pamphlets, banner, Canopy, Invitations, etc.
- Design post for Social Media sites and Web.

Education

University of Rajasthan, Jaipur

Master of visual art, 2017

Mahatma Jyoti Rao Phoole University, Jaipur

Bachelor of visual arts, 2015

Senior Secondary

Rajasthan Board, 2011

Certification

Certified in Adobe Illustrator

Achievements

2011-2015: Gold Medalist in Bachelor of Visual Art with Distinction.

2015: Won 1st prize in Painting Competition held at Rajasthan University

2012: Won 1st prize in Rangoli Competition held at M.J.R.P. University.